GAIL Y. W. BEST

email: gaylebe@hotmail.com

Tel: 428-3538/255-9818

15 Seaview Road, Chancery Lane Christ Church

MOTIVATED, DEDICATED SELF-STARTER WITH THE ABILITY TO WORK INDEPENDENTLY

Detailed-oriented, Analytical, Accurate Professional with vast experience working as an Executive Assistant for over 15 years. A quick learner and strong organizer who can juggle competing priorities in a fast-paced environment. I am also willing to pursue further training and studies.

AREAS OF KNOWLEDGE

Technical Skills: Microsoft Office - Word, Excel, Power Point, Outlook

PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION AND TRAINING

The St. Michael School
The Samuel Jackman Prescod Polytechnic - Shorthand
The Barbados Insurance Institute - Barbados Diploma of
Insurance
CGA - Financial Accounting 1 - Pass

Courses Completed

- Managing Contractor Safety Performance The Safety Council of Trinidad & Tobago
- Risk Assessment & Management Caribbean Institute for Quality Ltd.

Modules Covered - Understanding Risks - Accident Impact

- The Risk Assessment Process
- Managing & Controlling Risks
- Risk Communication
- Behaviour Based Safety
- Industrial Relations BIMAP
- Working Safely Institution of Occupational Safety & Health
- Accident & Incident Investigation REA Envirohealth
- Indoor Air Quality & Mould Awareness REA Envirohealth

WORK EXPERIENCE

UNITED INSURANCE COMPANY LIMITED

1989 to 1999

Secretary to Overseas Manager

- Liaise with agencies in Caribbean territories with respect to planning meetings, providing insurance quotations.
- Overseeing investments in the overseas territories.
- General secretarial and administrative duties.

SEAWELL AIR SERVICES LTD.

1999 - March 2013

Executive Assistant to the CEO and Health & Safety Officer

- Prepare Ground Handling contracts for the airlines
- Assist Airlines with obtaining Landing and Technical permits for operation into Barbados.
- Attend meetings and record minutes
- Organize meetings and travel itineraries
- Maintain attendance records for all staff
- Maintain an efficient and up-to-date filing system

- Maintain records for Ministry of International Transport and Airport Manager's Office with respect to staff passes, security clearance etc.
- Liaise with The Ministry of International Transport and other Government Agencies with respect to Airline requirements and regulations.
- Liaise with Head Office with reference to various staff issues.
- Prepare and present monthly Health & Safety reports.
- Ensure company is compliant with Safety and Health At Work Act.
- Intercept and resolve Health & Safety concerns.
- Other secretarial and administrative duties.

UNITED INSURANCE COMPANY LIMITED

March 2013 to August 2013 Administrative Assistant

- Prepare and issue Insurance Policies
- Maintain files
- General Secretarial Duties

MASSY DISTRIBUTION (BARBADOS) LTD.

August 2013 to April 2016 Executive Assistant to the Board of Directors (7 persons). Daily duties include:

- Respond to general correspondence.
- Manage daily appointments for the Directors
- Ordering of stationery and other materials for company.
- Liaising with FLOW re: corporate account for staff of approximately 215 cell phone users.
- Maintaining vehicular details (Drivers' Licenses, Road Tax and Insurance) for staff who operate vehicles on behalf of company.
- Responding to and logging Customer Complaints.
- Making travel arrangements including accommodation for Directors and Managers.
- Arranging Meetings and recording Minutes.

ASSOCIATIONS

Former Member of The Board of Directors - Lifetime Cooperative Credit Union.

REFERENCES

Mr. Dale Hunte Human Resources Manager Massy Barbados Warrens Tel: 233-2752

Philip F. Corbin Former CEO - Seawell Air Services Ltd. Valley View St. George

Tel: 429-1917/256-7415